Guide to the Larry John Meyers Papers, 1980-2015 CTC.2012.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Larry John Meyers Papers
1980-2015
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Meyers, Larry John
CTC.2012.03
10 Linear Feet (22 document boxes)
Larry John Meyers has been an actor and director in the Pittsburgh performing arts community for over 30 years. He has worked extensively with the City Theatre, the Pittsburgh Public Theatre, The Pittsburgh Irish & Classical Theatre, and the University of Pittsburgh Repertory Theatre. This collection contains film and play scripts, programs, promotional materials, rehearsal items, and newspaper clippings.
Biography
Larry John Meyers graduated from Luther College in Decorah, Iowa with a Bachelor of Arts in Speech and Theatre in 1972. He obtained his Master of Fine Arts degree in Acting from New York University's School of the Arts in 1979. Meyers has served as an actor, director, and instructor in the theatre community. His regional acting credits include La Mama (NYC), Actors Theatre of Louisville, Alabama Shakespeare Festival, Berkeley Rep, Chester Theatre (Massachusetts), Dallas Theater Center, Florida Rep, Indianapolis Rep, Minneapolis Children's Theater, Syracuse Stage, and Weston Playhouse (Vermont). His film and television acting credits include, American Splendor, Up Close & Personal, Runaway Train, Flashdance and Daddy Cool. Meyers has been an actor and director for over thirty years in Pittsburgh theater community as a founding company member of the New City Theatre (1981), member of the Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival, and many notable performances at the Pittsburgh Public Theater, City Theatre, Pittsburgh Irish & Classical Theatre, Quantum Theatre, Playhouse Rep, CMU's New Play Festivals, Pittsburgh Symphony, and Hartwood Acres. He served as a guest artist/teacher at Carnegie Mellon University, University of Pittsburgh, and Point Park College where he directed the critically acclaimed productions of Pericles (University of Pittsburgh), The Heiress (Point Park College), and for City Theatre: Bricklayers, Ladyhouse Blues, and The Road to Mecca ("Best Production of the Decade," Pittsburgh Post-Gazette, 1999). Meyers has won several awards and citations including the Bodensteiner Award at Luther College for Best Graduating Actor (1972), the Seidman Award at NYU for Best Graduating Actor (1979), the Pittsburgh Post-Gazette Performer of the Year (1992), three-time nominee for Creative Achievement award from the Pittsburgh Cultural Trust, and was the first recipient of Pittsburgh Foundation's Individual Artist Award in the Performing Arts (1998).
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Larry John Meyers in 2012.
Related Material
City Theatre Company Records, 1973-1993, CTC.1991.01, Curtis Theatre Collection, Archives & Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Iron Clad Agreement Records, 1975-1985, CTC.1990.01, Curtis Theatre Collection, Archives & Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Pittsburgh Irish and Classical Theatre Records, 1997-2015, CTC.2009.02, Curtis Theatre Collection, Archives & Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Pittsburgh Playhouse School of the Theater Records, 1934-1994, CTC.1981.01, Curtis Theatre Collection, Archives & Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival Records, 1980-1995, CTC.1995.01, Curtis Theatre Collection, Archives & Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh Library System
University of Pittsburgh Theatre Arts Department Records, 1960-1986, CTC.1974.02, Curtis Theatre Collection, Archives & Special Collections Department, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Arrangement
The papers are organized into three series.
Series I. Film Projects, 1984-2010
Series II. Non-Pittsburgh Productions, 1985-2014
Series III. Pittsburgh Productions, 1980-2015
Scope and Content Notes
This collection of Mr. Meyers' film and play scripts with related materials is broken into three main series: Film Projects, Non-Pittsburgh Productions, and Pittsburgh Productions. Both the Film and Non-Pittsburgh series are organized alphabetically by production title. The Pittsburgh series is broken into a subseries for each production company and then alphabetically by production title. The types of materals found in the collection includes promotional materials, rehearsal items, newspaper clippings, programs, and full or partial film and theatre scripts.
Motion picture scripts; Actors and actresses; Theater -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Performing arts -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; College theater -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Meyers, Larry John; City Theatre Company (Pittsburgh, Pa.); City Players (Pittsburgh, Pa.); University of Pittsburgh. Department of Theatre Arts; Three Rivers Shakespeare Festival (Pittsburgh, Pa.); Pittsburgh Playhouse. School of the Theater
- Film Projects, 1984-2010; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series collects the materials related to Meyers' film projects. The folders are arranged alphabetically by the film's title. Some of the materials included are call sheets, newspaper clippings, and production information. The majority also include a copy of scripts, excluding Breathing Lessons, Criminal Justice, and The Dream Catcher. The last folder of the series contains call sheets for films for which there were no other accompanying materials.
  - Breathing Lessons, June 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Director: John Erman
    Writers: Anne Tyler and Robert Lenski
    Production Company: Hallmark Hall of Fame Productions
    Release Date: 1994
  - Criminal Justice, March 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Director: Andy Wolk Writer: Andy Wolk Production Company: Elysian Films and Home Box Office Released: 1990
    This folder also contains an invitation to Pittsburgh premiere of Criminal Justice.
  - Daddy Cool, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Director: Brady Lewis Writer: Brady Lewis Production Company: Independent Release Date: 2002
  - The Dark Half, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Director: George Romero Writer: George Romero Production Company: Orion Pictures Corporation Release Date: 1993
    This folder also contains the January 1991 edition of Pittsburgh featuring George Romero as "Pittsburgher of the Year".
  - Darrow, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Director: John David Coles Writers: William Schmidt and Stephen Stept Production Company: Atlantis Films Release Date: 1991
  - The Dream Catcher, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Director: Ed Radtke Writers: M.S. Nieson and Ed Radtke Production Company: Film Society of Lincoln Center Release Date: 1999
  - Graduation, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Director: Mike Mayer Writer: D. Cory Turner Production Company: Blumhouse Productions Release Date: 2007
  - Maria's Lovers, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Director: Andrei Konchalovsky Writers: Gerard Brach, Andrei Konchalovsky, Paul Zindel, Marjorie David, and Floyd Byars Production Company: MGM Release Date: 1984
  - Milk Crate, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Director: John Rice Writer: John Rice Production Company: Pittsburgh 250 Celebration Release Date: 2008
  - The Murder, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Director: Greg Rempel Writer: Greg Rempel Production Company: Greg Rempel Productions, Inc. Release Date: 2002
    This folder also contains a letter from Greg Rempel Productions about the filming.
  - No Pets, 1992-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Director: Tony Buba Writer: Jim Daniels Production Company: Braddock Films Release Date: 1994
    This folder also contains a letter from Tony Buba (director) to Larry John Meyers.
  - No Place Like Home, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Director: Lee Grant Writers: Ara Watson and Sam Blackwell Production Company: Columbia Broadcasting System (CBS) Release Date: 1989
  - Passed Away, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Director: Charlie Peters Writer: Charlie Peters Production Company: Hollywood Pictures Release Date: 1992
  - A Resurrection, 2010 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Director: Matthew Orlando Writer: Matthew Orlando Production Company: Levine Pictures Release Date: 2013
    The paperwork / script are from when the film was titled The Sibling. The film name changed to A Resurrection prior to release.
  - Runaway Train, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Director: Andrei Konchalovsky Writers: Djordje Milicevic and Edward Bunker Production Company: Northbrook Films Release Date: 1985
  - Two Evil Eyes, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Directors: Dario Argento and George A. Romero Writers: Dario Argento, Franco Ferrini, Peter Koper, and George A. Romero Production Company: ADC Films Release Date: 1990
  - The War that Made America, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Directors: Ben Loeterman and Eric Stange Writers: Ben Loeterman and Eric Stange Production Company: PBS - WQED Pittsburgh Release Date: 2006
  - Call Sheets for Various Films, 1988-1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Call sheets are included for See No Evil, Hear No Evil (1988), Presumed Guilty (1991), Mob Justice (1991), and Equal Justice (1991).
- Non-Pittsburgh Productions, 1985-2014; II.
  This series collects the materials related to productions Meyer's was involved in outside of Pittsburgh, PA. The folders are arranged alphabetically by the production's title. Some of the materials included are personal cards and letters (from fans, friends, and colleagues), promotional materials, rehearsal items, and news clippings. Approximately half of the production files contain scripts. All of the productions, excluding A Lesson Before Dying, Pure Confidence, The Shaker Chair, and Wild Blessings (Perry Mansfield New Works Festival), contain programs.
  - Bang the Drum Slowly, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Author: Mark Harris Director: Eric Simonson Company: Huntington Theatre Company Performance Dates: March 11 - April 10, 1994
  - A Christmas Carol, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Author: Charles Dickens Adapted by: Adrian Hall and Richard Cumming Director: Martin Rayner Company: Dallas Theater Center Performance Dates: November 29 - December 27, 1987
  - Clybourne Park, 2014 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Author: Bruce Norris Director: Robert Cacioppo Company: Florida Repertory Theatre Performance Dates: March 22 - April 9, 2014
  - Communicating Doors, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Author: Alan Ayckbourn Director: Richard Keitel Company: Saint Michael's Playhouse Performance Dates: July 18 - 29, 2000
  - The Crucible - Actors Theatre of Louisville, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Author: Arthur Miller Director: Marc Masterson Company: Actors Theatre of Louisville Performance Dates: October 25 - November 19, 2005
  - The Crucible - Syracuse Stage, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Author: Arthur Miller Director: Timothy Douglas Company: Syracuse Stage Performance Dates: February 19 - March 22, 2003
    This folder also contains photographs from the production.
  - Fatal Attraction, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Author: Bernard Slade Director: Roger Hendricks Simon Company: Montclair State College Theatrefest
  - The Front Page, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Authors: Ben Hecht and Charles MacArthur Director: Tom Haas Company: Indiana Repertory Theatre Performance Dates: October 25 - November 16, 1985
  - Gem of the Ocean - Actors Theatre of Louisville, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    Author: August Wilson
    Director: Ron OJ Parson
    Company: Actors Theatre of Louisville
    Performance Dates: March 3 - 28, 2006
    This folder also contains CDs from the production.
  - Gershwin!, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Author: Jack Everly Music Director Designate: Yur Temirkanov Company: Baltimore Symphony Orchestra Performance Dates: October 1 - 4, 1998
  - Glengarry Glen Ross, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Author: David Mamet Director: Marc Masterson Company: Actors Theatre of Louisville Performance Dates: August 26 - September 20, 2008
  - Humana Festival, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Plays Performed: Memory House, Pure Confidence, Hazard County, A Nervous Smile, The Shaker Chair, Moot the Messenger Company: Actors Theatre of Louisville Festival Dates: April 2 - 30, 2005
  - I'm Getting My Act Together and Taking it on the Road, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Author: Gretchen Cryer Director: Tom Carroll Company: Montclair State College Summerfest Performance Dates: July 21 - August 1, 1987
  - A Lesson Before Dying, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
    Author: Romulus Linney Director: Timothy Douglas Company: Syracuse Stage Performance Dates: February 14 - March 9, 2002
    This folder also contains a floppy disk and an autographed photograph from the production.
  - Line in the Sand, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Author: Chris Hanna Director: Timothy Douglas Company: Virginia Stage Company Performance Date: May 10, 2008
  - Lovers and Other Strangers, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Authors: Renee Taylor and Joseph Bologna Director: Laurence Gewirtz Company: Liberty Stage Company
  - Molly Sweeney, 2000 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Author: Brian Friel Director: Steve Stettler Company: Weston Playhouse Performance Dates: October 12 - 15, 2000
  - Noises Off, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    Author: Michael Frayn Director: Ken Bryant Company: Dallas Theater Center Performance Dates: October 7 - 26, 1986
  - A Number, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Author: Caryl Churchill Director: Byam Stevens Company: Chester Theatre Company Performance Dates: July 30 - August 10, 2014
  - O Beautiful, 2014 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    Author: Theresa Rebeck Director: Dan Carter Company: Penn State Centre Stage Performance Dates: October 7 - 18, 2014
  - Perry-Mansfield New Works Festival, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    Company: Perry-Mansfield Performing Arts School and Camp Festival Dates: June 11 - 22, 2008
  - Pure Confidence - Actors Theatre of Louisville, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    Author: Carlyle Brown Director: Clinton Turner Davis Company: Actors Theatre of Louisville Performance Dates: March 17 - April 9, 2005
  - Pure Confidence - Alabama Shakespeare Festival, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    Author: Carlyle Brown Director: Clinton Turner Davis Company: Alabama Shakespeare Festival Performance Dates: January 22 - February 19, 2006
  - The Shaker Chair, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    Author: Adam Bock Director: Marc Masterson Company: Actors Theatre of Louisville Performance Dates: March 8 - April 2, 2005
  - The Small Legacy, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    Author: Todd Kreidler Director: Todd Kreidler Company: Sparkly Productions Festival: Telluride Playwrights Festival Performance Date: July 14, 2009
  - Three Sisters, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Author: Anton Chekov Director: Rena Down Company: Equity Library Theatre Performance Dates: April 17 - May 4, 1986
  - To Gillian on her 37th Birthday, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Author: Michael Brady Director: Robert Spera Company: Montclair State College Summerfest Performance Dates: July 4 - 26, 1986
  - Variations on America - A Work in Progress, 2004 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Author: John Conklin Director: John Conklin Company: National Performing Arts Convention Performance Dates: June 8 - 13, 2004
  - Wild Blessings - Humana Festival, 2009 (Box 6, Folder 6-8)
    Author: Marc Masterson and Adrien-Alice Hansel Director: Marc Masterson Company: Actors Theatre of Louisville Festival: Humana Festival Performance Dates: March 26 - April 11, 2009
  - Wild Blessings - Perry Mansfield New Works Festival, 2008 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Author: Marc Masterson and Adrien-Alice Hansel Director: Marc Masterson Company: Actors Theatre of Louisville Festival: Perry Mansfield New Works Festival Performance Dates: June 20 - 22, 2008
- Pittsburgh Productions, 1980-2015; III.
  This series collects the materials related to Pittsburgh productions Meyer's was involved in. The folders are arranged alphabetically by the production title for each Pittsburgh company. Some of the materials included are personal cards and letters (from fans, friends, and colleagues), promotional materials, rehearsal items, and news clippings. Approximately half of the production files contain programs. The majority of the productions contain full or partial scripts.
  - Carnegie Mellon School of Drama, 1988-2008
    - Carnegie Mellon Drama's Showcase of New Plays, 1989-1991 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      Productions: By Reason of an Act of God, Love and Murder, The Duck Sisters, The Closer, Spinning Into Blue, Steel Kiss, The Gravity of Honey, The Battle of Shallowford, Accelerando, Connemara Dreaming
      Authors: Brent London, Arthur Giron, Sheldon Rosen, Willy Holtzman, Sally Nemeth, Robin Fulford, Bruce Rogers, Ed Simpson, Lisa Loomer, Jack Gilhooley
      Directors: Jed Allen Harris, Scott Cummings, Michelle Macau, Brian Kulick, Rick Davis, Jed Allen Harris, Brian Kulick, Mary Guaraldi, Jed Allen Harris, Bob Hofmann
      Performance Dates: 1988-1990
    - George Westinghouse project, March 2008 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      Larry John Meyers portrayed George Westinghouse as part of an interactive exhibit on the historical figure at the Heinz History Center. The performance was produced by and filmed at Carnegie Mellon University's Entertainment Technology Center.
  - City Theatre, 1981-2007
    - Acting Up!, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Author: City Theatre Group Director: Marc Masterson Performance Dates: Touring Performances, 1983
    - Below the Belt, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Author: Richard Dresser Director: Marc Masterson Performance Dates: February 21 - March 16, 1997
    - Bricklayers, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      Author: Elvira DiPaolo Director: Larry John Meyers Performance Dates: November 30 - December 22, 1991
      This folder also contains audition materials and stage designs.
    - Curse of the Starving Class, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      Author: Sam Shepard Director: Jed Allen Harris Performance Dates: November 7 - 29, 1981
    - How I Got That Story, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      Author: Amlin Gray Director: Jed Allen Harris Performance Dates: January 13 - February 6, 1983
    - Indians, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      Author: Author Kopit Director: Marc Masterson Performance Dates: February 11 - March 7, 1982
      This folder also contains a program and news articles for the "Buffalo Bill and the Wild West" exhibit at the Carnegie Museum of Art.
    - Inventing Van Gogh, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      Author: Steven Dietz Director: Neel Keller Performance Dates: September 19 - October 20, 2002
    - Ladyhouse Blues, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      Author: Kevin O'Morrison Director: Larry John Meyers Performance Dates: February 17 - March 13, 1983
    - Loose Ends, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      Author: Michael Weller Director: Larry John Meyers Performance Dates: March 25 - April 18, 1982
    - Louder Faster, 2010 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      Authors: Eric Simonson and Jeffrey Hatcher Performance Dates: Stage Reading May 7 - 29, 2011
      This folder contains the script for the stage reading of Louder Faster at Momentum 11.
    - Mezzulah, 1946, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 13-14)
      Author: Michele Lowe Director: Erica Schmidt Performance Dates: March 14 - April 1, 2007
      This folder also contains photographs from this production.
    - Mobile Hymn, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      Author: Robert Litz Director: Jed Allen Harris Performance Dates: March 24 - April 16, 1983
    - Molly Sweeney, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      Author: Brian Friel Director: Lee Sankowich Performance Dates: April 11 - May 4, 1997
    - Mrs. Bob Cratchit's Wild Christmas Binge, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 3-4)
      Author: Christopher Durang Director: Tracy Brigden Performance Dates: November 7 - December 15, 2002
    - The Road to Mecca, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      Author: Athol Fuggard Director: Larry John Meyers Performance Dates: March 20 - April 21, 1991
    - Shakespeare's Swashbuckler's (Box 8, Folder 6)
      Author: City Theatre Company Director: W. Stephen Coleman Performance Dates: Touring Performance, 1981
      This folder contains a handwritten script to describe swashbuckling and scripts from Shakespearean swashbuckling scenes including Romeo & Juliet, Henry IV, Twelfth Night, King Lear, and Hamlet.
    - Side Man, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      Author: Warren Leight Director: Mladen Kiselov Performance Dates: November 10 - December 10, 2000
    - Temptation, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Author: Václav Havel Director: Mladen Kiselov Performance Dates: April 16 - May 16, 1993
    - Working, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      Author: Studs Terkel Adaptation by: Stephen Schwartz and Nina Faso Directors: Marc Masteron and Ken Gargaro Performance Dates: October 7 - 31, 1982
  - International Poetry Forum
    - Sexes: The Marriage Dialogues, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Author: Samuel Hazo Director: Samuel Hazo Performance Dates: October 15, 2008
      This folder contains the Sexes: The Marriage Dialogues book.
  - Iron Clad Agreement, 1980-1981
    - Various Productions, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      This folder contains a program for Gift to America (1980) and The Spirit of Mercy (1981), 1981 promotional mailings and employment letters, The Iron Clad Rag (the Iron Clad Agreement Newsletter), news clippings and flyer for Interchangeable Parts, news clippings for Art/Work, promotional mailings and lyrics for Toymaker, and a cast photograph
  - Off the Record, 2003-2011
    - Off the Record III: Lights! Pittsburgh! Action!, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      Authors: Gary Rotstein and Dan Kamin Company: Off the Record; collaboration of unionized members of Southwestern Pennsylvania's media and theater worlds Director: Gregory Lehane Performance Dates: October 2, 2003 Performed at the Byham Theatre
    - Off the Record XI: No Fracking Way!, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Author: Gary Rotstein Company: Off the Record; collaboration of unionized members of Southwestern Pennsylvania's media and theater worlds Director: Gregory Lehane Performance Dates: October 6, 2011 Performed at the Byham Theatre
  - Pittsburgh Chamber Music Society, 2005
    - Bartók Night, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      Author: Lynne Conner Director: Lynne Conner Performance Dates: October 29, 2005
  - The Pittsburgh Cleric, 2005
    - As Heaven Intends or Hell Designs, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      Adaptation by: George Bernard Shaw Director: Larry John Meyers Performance Date: May 9, 2005 Performed at the Shadyside Presbyterian Church
      Larry John Meyers: Narrator, Devil
  - Pittsburgh Irish & Classical Theatre, 2002-2014
    - Aristocrats, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      Author: Brian Friel Director: Andrew S. Paul Performance Dates: August 8 - 24, 2002
    - Copenhagen, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Author: Michael Frayn Director: Gregory Lehane Performance Dates: June 10 - August 2, 2003 and November 7 - 23, 2003
    - Crime and Punishment, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      Author: Fyodor Dostoevsky Adapted by: Marilyn Campbell and Curt Columbus Director: Matthew Gray Performance Dates: September 10 - October 3, 2009
    - The Cripple of Inishmaan, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      Author: Martin McDonagh Director: Timothy Douglas Performance Dates: June 8 - 24, 2000
    - The Dead, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      Author: James Joyce Director: Scott Wise Performance Dates: December 2 - 18, 2004
    - Dublin Carol, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 3-5)
      Author: Conor McPherson Director: Jackie Maxwell Performance Dates: December 6 - 20, 2008
      These folders also contain Meyers' personal notebooks with handwritten lines from the script for memorization.
    - The End, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      Author: Samuel Beckett Performance Dates: Staged Reading, June 13 - 14, 2004
    - Endgame, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 7-8)
      Author: Samuel Beckett Director: Tadeusz Bradecki Performance Dates: August 17 - September 10, 2006
    - First Love, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Author: Samuel Beckett Performance Dates: Stage Reading June 9 - 10, 2002
    - The Gigli Concert, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 1)